const questions = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question:
        "Which of the following statements best describes the Law of Conservation of Energy?",
      options: [
        "Energy can be created but not destroyed.",
        "Energy can be destroyed but not created.",
        "Energy cannot be created or destroyed, only transferred or transformed.",
        "Energy can be transferred but not transformed.",
      ],
      answer: 0,
      explain: 'The Law of Conservation of Energy is a fundamental principle in physics that states that the total amount of energy in an isolated system remains constant over time. Energy cannot be created out of nothing or destroyed completely. It can only change its form or be transferred from one object or system to another. This principle holds true for all types of energy, including kinetic energy, potential energy, thermal energy, electromagnetic energy, and others.'
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question:
        "Which of the following statements best describes the Law of Conservation of Energy 2?",
      options: [
        "Energy can be created but not destroyed.",
        "Energy can be destroyed but not created.",
        "Energy cannot be created or destroyed, only transferred or transformed.",
        "Energy can be transferred but not transformed.",
      ],
      answer: 2,
      explain: 'The Law of Conservation of Energy is a fundamental principle in physics that states that the total amount of energy in an isolated system remains constant over time. Energy cannot be created out of nothing or destroyed completely. It can only change its form or be transferred from one object or system to another. This principle holds true for all types of energy, including kinetic energy, potential energy, thermal energy, electromagnetic energy, and others.'

    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question:
        "Which of the following statements best describes the Law of Conservation of Energy? 3",
      options: [
        "Energy can be created but not destroyed.",
        "Energy can be destroyed but not created.",
        "Energy cannot be created or destroyed, only transferred or transformed.",
        "Energy can be transferred but not transformed.",
      ],
      answer: 0,
      explain: 'The Law of Conservation of Energy is a fundamental principle in physics that states that the total amount of energy in an isolated system remains constant over time. Energy cannot be created out of nothing or destroyed completely. It can only change its form or be transferred from one object or system to another. This principle holds true for all types of energy, including kinetic energy, potential energy, thermal energy, electromagnetic energy, and others.'

    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question:
        "Which of the following statements best describes the Law of Conservation of Energy? 4",
      options: [
        "Energy can be created but not destroyed.",
        "Energy can be destroyed but not created.",
        "Energy cannot be created or destroyed, only transferred or transformed.",
        "Energy can be transferred but not transformed.",
      ],
      answer: 3,
      explain: 'The Law of Conservation of Energy is a fundamental principle in physics that states that the total amount of energy in an isolated system remains constant over time. Energy cannot be created out of nothing or destroyed completely. It can only change its form or be transferred from one object or system to another. This principle holds true for all types of energy, including kinetic energy, potential energy, thermal energy, electromagnetic energy, and others.'

    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question:
        "Which of the following statements best describes the Law of Conservation of Energy? 5",
      options: [
        "Energy can be created but not destroyed.",
        "Energy can be destroyed but not created.",
        "Energy cannot be created or destroyed, only transferred or transformed.",
        "Energy can be transferred but not transformed.",
      ],
      answer: 1,
      explain: 'The Law of Conservation of Energy is a fundamental principle in physics that states that the total amount of energy in an isolated system remains constant over time. Energy cannot be created out of nothing or destroyed completely. It can only change its form or be transferred from one object or system to another. This principle holds true for all types of energy, including kinetic energy, potential energy, thermal energy, electromagnetic energy, and others.'

    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question:
        "Which of the following statements best describes the Law of Conservation of Energy? 6",
      options: [
        "Energy can be created but not destroyed.",
        "Energy can be destroyed but not created.",
        "Energy cannot be created or destroyed, only transferred or transformed.",
        "Energy can be transferred but not transformed.",
      ],
      answer: 1,
      explain: 'The Law of Conservation of Energy is a fundamental principle in physics that states that the total amount of energy in an isolated system remains constant over time. Energy cannot be created out of nothing or destroyed completely. It can only change its form or be transferred from one object or system to another. This principle holds true for all types of energy, including kinetic energy, potential energy, thermal energy, electromagnetic energy, and others.'

    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question:
        "Which of the following statements best describes the Law of Conservation of Energy? 7",
      options: [
        "Energy can be created but not destroyed.",
        "Energy can be destroyed but not created.",
        "Energy cannot be created or destroyed, only transferred or transformed.",
        "Energy can be transferred but not transformed.",
      ],
      answer: 0,
      explain: 'The Law of Conservation of Energy is a fundamental principle in physics that states that the total amount of energy in an isolated system remains constant over time. Energy cannot be created out of nothing or destroyed completely. It can only change its form or be transferred from one object or system to another. This principle holds true for all types of energy, including kinetic energy, potential energy, thermal energy, electromagnetic energy, and others.'

    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question:
        "Which of the following statements best describes the Law of Conservation of Energy? 8",
      options: [
        "Energy can be created but not destroyed.",
        "Energy can be destroyed but not created.",
        "Energy cannot be created or destroyed, only transferred or transformed.",
        "Energy can be transferred but not transformed.",
      ],
      answer: 0,
      explain: 'The Law of Conservation of Energy is a fundamental principle in physics that states that the total amount of energy in an isolated system remains constant over time. Energy cannot be created out of nothing or destroyed completely. It can only change its form or be transferred from one object or system to another. This principle holds true for all types of energy, including kinetic energy, potential energy, thermal energy, electromagnetic energy, and others.'

    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question:
        "Which of the following statements best describes the Law of Conservation of Energy? 9",
      options: [
        "Energy can be created but not destroyed.",
        "Energy can be destroyed but not created.",
        "Energy cannot be created or destroyed, only transferred or transformed.",
        "Energy can be transferred but not transformed.",
      ],
      answer: 1,
      explain: 'The Law of Conservation of Energy is a fundamental principle in physics that states that the total amount of energy in an isolated system remains constant over time. Energy cannot be created out of nothing or destroyed completely. It can only change its form or be transferred from one object or system to another. This principle holds true for all types of energy, including kinetic energy, potential energy, thermal energy, electromagnetic energy, and others.'

    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question:
        "Which of the following statements best describes the Law of Conservation of Energy? 10",
      options: [
        "Energy can be created but not destroyed.",
        "Energy can be destroyed but not created.",
        "Energy cannot be created or destroyed, only transferred or transformed.",
        "Energy can be transferred but not transformed.",
      ],
      answer: 3,
      explain: 'The Law of Conservation of Energy is a fundamental principle in physics that states that the total amount of energy in an isolated system remains constant over time. Energy cannot be created out of nothing or destroyed completely. It can only change its form or be transferred from one object or system to another. This principle holds true for all types of energy, including kinetic energy, potential energy, thermal energy, electromagnetic energy, and others.'

    },
  ];
  
  export default questions;

  export const answers = [1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 1, 0, 0, 2, 2]